[Music] It has happened
[Music] It has happened [Music
]
Picture of do it
[Music]
So in the time of Corona, all the business, jobs
and all the financial resources are closed. In such a situation, if
we have to spend a few lakh rupees in the hospital
due to some illness, then it will have a
huge impact on our financial condition.
According to all the media reports, the Naxalite
threat will start when the long term lockdown opens, when we
all go out, that is, if you do
not take health insurance today, then
even after the long term lockdown opens, you will
not have any mental protection available. Just imagine,
if today, despite having money, we are delaying in paying the premium of
20 thousand rupees to the health insurance policy squad, then in such a situation,
if we have to pay a few lakh rupees, then
we will be in so much trouble. Today, in the
race of lockdown, we are all ready to order food or mobile online,
but
we do not have time to think that health insurance policy is available at home tomorrow.
Get a health insurance policy today and save your business or savings money from
going to the hospital and save them
and its brother. Today, before starting the video,
I want to thank all of you.  I would like to thank you very much for the way
you
liked our video so much. Thank you for your
comments and feedback. I support you like this,
I am your help consultant.
So let's start the video. In today's
video, we will learn about Bajaj Allianz company's
health insurance plan, Health Guard.
It will give you two balances
in Silver and Gold. Friends, you will be able to
subscribe for up to ₹100 and
people can take this loan at this age. The
age limit is from 18 years to 3
months to 30 years. If we
talk about the policy, you get the policy
for life time. The
policy period is 3 years and
you can also pay the premium of the policy for your family in Chali and Man
Indore. It
is available to you on both individual and family floater basis. You will talk
about the benefits of the policy.
First of all, you get the benefit of Information Hospital Insurance, in
which in the Silver plan
you will get 1% on room rent and 10 minutes per day or even
less than this.  And there is no limit on room rent,
you get it, in
which the subscription is for parties and
you get a maximum of 20,000 rupees for days.
Apart from this, see the list in the policy,
treatment is also covered for you and donor
expenses are awarded to you, this
means if someone donates to you then
you have to bear a lot of expenses for that, so
this covers your organ donor expenses.
Please subscribe, then
you have some benefits, it is said that
you get
₹5000 and if you subscribe then
you get this and you can also take this benefit in your policy,
if you
get a benefit of ₹500 maximum
for photos. One thing in the policy,
if you stay with a small child
in the hospital during his treatment, to get this benefit
also, your policy term should be more than one year.
Apart from all this,
you only get the benefit of seven inches and beans statement.
This means that in this policy, if
your health becomes
10 in the middle of the policy due to the clinic, then with the
help of which benefit you will get the
right hundred percent assurance, there is a
benefit of free health check-up, you
get it this year if you are Android in this policy for
three consecutive years, then
in Shilpagram you get 1% top
10 Tamil short maximum ₹2000 and in volume
you get a checkup benefit of maximum ₹5000,
let's know
about the other benefits which you get only votes,
your eye treatment expenses,
school set back are covered, this means
if you get your treatment done in Ayurvedic and Homeopathic hospital, then
you get
express Islamic news of maximum 20 thousand rupees,
due to which you get delivery, if your time is
low then you get 3 lakh to 7.5 lakh normal
delivery, you get 15000 delivery and
if you get fixed from 10 lakh to ₹5
You get ₹50, you get it, now let us
know about it
that in the Charter Act, you get 20% and
10 more limits on studies,
you get treatment up to a maximum of 1 lakh, this is the term and
on bariatric surgery, you get 50%
of the same joint, maximum limit up to ₹5000,
now we will talk about Islam's
waiting ticket, so the initial
waiting period is 30 days, for West Indies,
you get a waiting period of 24,
for pre-existing disease and bariatric surgery, you get a
waiting period of 36 months and for
taking maternity benefit, you get a
waiting period of 1972 months, apart from these,
you get a free look period of 15 days
and cancellation facility
is also available, in Islam you get the
benefit of kissing bonus, temples and maximum
two hundred percent, in Islam you get
people below 45 years of age for any major medical  There is
no need for a check-up, friends,
this is
good information about the
health insurance plan Health Guard of Bajaj Finance Company, through which
you can get it, please
tell me how you liked this video, if it is
related to a doctor then ask him and
if you like this video on WhatsApp, then
definitely share the video with your relatives, it will
help them and do
not forget to subscribe to the channel, like it
so that such videos are not available for you, click on the bell icon so
that you can get first of all thank you for
watching my video,
hello friends, the page to help you, to give you, have
read for the only, it provides you free
health check-up, today in this video I will
tell you about the software, you
type gas, you
can decide your website, so
we will know about it in car speed, you will translate your feet, do it, do it